so greetings my friends dealing with sin
所以问候我的朋友处理罪恶
biblically well sin is one of the most
圣经上好罪是其中之一
important topics in counseling and in
辅导和重要议题
life and so the biblical counselor
生活等等圣经辅导员
regards sin as evil against a holy God
将罪视为对神圣的上帝的邪恶
and we also believe that each person is
我们也相信每个人都是
responsible for their own sins many
对自己的罪负责很多
biblical counseling cases can be
圣经咨询案例可以
summarized in this one sentence through
总结在这一句话中
God's efficient grace and his sufficient
上帝的有效恩典和他的充足
word a Christian overcame a habit
一句基督徒克服了一个习惯
pattern of sin the Bible has solutions
圣经有罪的模式有解决方案
for man's problems with sin for the
为了男人的罪的问题
unbeliever forgiveness and a new life
不信的宽恕和新的生活
are available through the gospel and for
都可以通过福音和
the believer the Bible promises the
圣经承诺的信徒
ability to overcome sin let's start with
克服罪恶的能力让我们开始吧
the unsaved counsel II we talked a bit
未得救的律师我们谈了一下
about that person last night let's break
关于那个人昨晚让我们休息
it down a little more this morning the
它今天早上多了一点
unsaved counsel II the first important
未得救的律师II第一重要
truth is that salvation of a human soul
真相就是人类灵魂的救赎
is God's work Ephesians 2 4 through 10
是上帝的工作以弗所书2 4到10
has these words God being rich in mercy
有这句话神既有丰富的怜悯
and because of his great love even when
而且因为他的爱，即使是
we were dead in our transgressions made
我们在犯罪中死了
us alive together with Christ by grace
我们与恩典一起活着
you have been saved through faith and
你通过信仰得救了
that not of yourselves it is a gift of
不是你自己这是礼物
God we are his workmanship
上帝，我们是他的工艺
so when counseling the unsaved person I
所以在为未得救的人提供咨询时我
communicate the gospel clearly and pray
清楚地传达福音并祈祷
for God to save the counselee
为了上帝拯救顾问
the gospel what is the gospel we talked
福音我们所谈论的福音是什么
about this a bit last night and it's
关于这一点昨晚，这是
important for us to be able to give a
对我们来说重要的是能够给予一个
biblical answer to the question what
圣经回答问题是什么
must I do to be saved
我必须做些什么来得救
this is a frequent occurrence in the
这是经常发生的事情
biblical counseling room Wayne Grudem in
圣经咨询室Wayne Grudemin
his systematic theology accurately
他的系统神学准确
writes the essential components of the
写的基本组成部分
gospel here's our quote from Grudem
福音这里是我们从Grudem引用的
explanation of the facts concerning
有关事实的解释
salvation anyone who comes to Christ for
拯救任何人谁来到基督
salvation must have at least a basic
救恩必须至少有一个基本的
understanding of who Christ is and how
了解基督是谁以及如何
he meets our needs for salvation
他满足了我们对救恩的需要
therefore an explanation of the facts
因此解释事实
concerning salvation must include at
关于救恩必须包括在
least the following one all people have
至少有以下一个所有的人都有
sinned Romans 3:23 - the penalty for sin
犯罪的罗马书3:23- 对罪的惩罚
is death Romans 6:23 and 3 Jesus Christ
是死罗马书6:23和3耶稣基督
died to pay the penalty for our sins
死要为我们的罪罚
Romans 5:8 he goes on invitation to
罗马书5：8 他应邀去
respond to Christ personally in
回应基督亲自
repentance and faith it is sufficient to
悔改和信仰就足够了
note here that if we come to Christ and
请注意，如果我们来到基督和
trust him to save us from our sin we
相信他把我们从我们的罪，我们保存
cannot any longer cling to sin but must
不能再坚持罪而必须
willingly renounce it in genuine
心甘情愿地放弃它
repentance acts 20:21
忏悔行为20:21
any genuine gospel Proclamation must
任何真正的福音宣言必须
include an invitation to make a
包括邀请做出一个
conscious decision to forsake one's sins
有意识地决定放弃一个人的罪过
and to come to Christ in faith asking
并以信心的方式来到基督面前
Christ for forgiveness of sins he
基督赦免他的罪
finishes if either the need to repent of
如果要么需要悔改就完成
sins or the need to trust Christ for
罪或需要信靠基督
forgiveness is neglected there is not a
宽恕被忽略不存在
full and true proclamation of the gospel
充分而真实地传播福音
end of quote
引用结束
in our time many people who have not
在我们这个时代很多人没有
repented
后悔
sinn who have not turned from as Roman
新芬谁没有从为罗马 打开
six as being slaves to sin to being
六是作为罪的奴隶
slaves of Christ many people in that
基督的奴隶很多人
group believe that they are Christians
小组认为他们是基督徒
they've heard an incomplete gospel that
他们听到了一个不完整的福音
does not include dying to the old self
不包括死于旧的自我
and being crucified with Christ
与基督同钉十字架
I've had many counsel ease struggling
我有许多建议轻松挣扎
with sin who believed that they were
与罪人相信他们是
Christians but the gospel that they had
基督徒， 但他们有福音
heard was something like this if they
如果他们听到的话是这样的
just believe they have the free gift of
只是相信他们有免费礼物
forgiveness through the blood of Christ
通过 基督的血赦免
they're free to sin in any way they wish
他们可以随心所欲地犯罪
because they're now saved from the
因为他们现在已经从中拯救了
penalty of sin and so that person in the
罪的惩罚使那个人在
counseling room it's confusing because
咨询室令人困惑，因为
they're going to church they responded
他们要教会他们回答
to the gospel they heard but sin is
他们听到了福音，但罪是
still dominating their life one man who
仍然统治着他们一生的人
came to me for counseling who attends a
来找我参加咨询的人
church that preaches a gospel without
没有传福音的教会
reference to sin or repentance told me
提到罪或悔改告诉我
about his regular weekend practice which
关于他的常规周末练习
would be drinking to the point of
会喝酒到了
intoxication and having sex with his
醉酒和与他发生性关系
girlfriend who lived with him in his
与他同住的女朋友
house every weekend so I showed him in
每个周末都有房子，所以我给他看了
the scriptures that both of these were
这些都是经文
sins and that ongoing immorality is a
罪和持续不道德是一个
sin that in a church following the
罪，在一所教堂继
scriptures would involve church
经文会涉及教会
discipline if he didn't repent according
纪律，如果他不思悔改，根据
to 1st Corinthians 5 9 through 13 here's
到哥林多前书5章9到13这里
what this man said church attender I've
这个男人说的教会参加者我是什么
read here's his quote I've read these
在这里阅读他的引用我读过这些
things in the Bible but I thought they
圣经中的东西，但我想他们
were outdated I don't think I've ever
已经过时我不认为我曾经
met a Christian who actually lived by
遇到了一位真正住过的基督徒
them end of quote well that day he met a
当那天他遇到了一个
Christian who lived by them but the
基督徒谁住他们但他们
point is there are a lot of people like
点是有很多人喜欢的
that in our
在我们的
world so it's important for us to
世界对我们来说非常重要
communicate a true and complete gospel
传达真实而完整的福音
message and in that way to best serve
消息，以这种方式，以最好的服务
counsel leaves in that group well
律师很好地离开了那个小组
because there are many people like that
因为有很多人喜欢这样
man in our culture it's vital to gather
在我们的文化中，聚集至关重要
good data early in our relationships
我们关系早期的良好数据
with people yesterday we talked about
我们昨天和人们谈过
the basic questions the gospel related
福音相关的基本问题
questions and we also talked about we
问题，我们也谈到了我们
also talked about the good diagnostic
还谈到了良好的诊断
questions in Romans six four through 14
罗马书六至四四的问题
and Romans eight six to thirteen really
和罗马人八六到十三真的
helpful along those lines with Romans
与罗马人一样有用
8:6 through thirteen I'd like to tell
8：6到13我想告诉你
you about one council II where this
你对一个议会II这个地方
particular passage was beneficial this
特别的段落对此有益
was a 17 year old who who had grown up
是一个17岁的人，长大了
in the church and was confident that he
在教堂，并相信他
was a Christian but he had these
是一个基督徒，但他有这些
conflicts in his life and so we read
在他的生活冲突，所以我们阅读
romans 6 or 8 6 through 13 and and then
罗马6或8 6到13然后
I asked him that question which one are
我问他那个问题是哪一个
you because the passage has two
你因为这段经文有两个
categories the person who's living in
把生活的人归类
the flesh and the person who's living
肉，谁的生活的人
according to the spirit it was really
根据它的精神真的
interesting what he did was he took out
有趣的是他做了什么，他拿出来了
a paper and pen and he said you know I
纸和笔， 他说你知道我
want to get this straight and so he just
要得到这个直等他只是
wrote down on his paper okay let's see
写下他的论文好吧让我们看看
living in the flesh here all the things
住在这里的肉 所有的东西
that this passage says about that and
这段经文谈到了这一点
wrote them all down and then he wrote
把它们写下来，然后他写道
down all the ones on the other side
在另一边的所有那些
living in the spirit this is what he
生活在精神中这就是他
said I want to be the person in the
说我想成为的人在
column on the right because I believe in
右边的栏目，因为我相信
God
神
and that there is a heaven and a hell
并且有一个天堂和一个地狱
but everything I do says that I am the
但我所做的一切说，我是
person in the column on the left that
左边那一列的那个人
was an important day he talked about how
是一个重要的日子，他谈到了如何
he lived for pleasure and he lived for
他过着快乐的生活而且为他而活
his own desires for him that meant
他对自己的渴望意味着什么
arguing with his parents a lot and
和他的父母争吵很多
seeking intimacy with his girlfriend
寻求与女友的亲密关系
that day he realized that the Bible
那天他意识到了圣经
teaches that repentance is a part of the
教导悔改是其中的一部分
response to the facts of the gospel
响应福音的事实
necessary for salvation I'm really
救恩所必需的我真的
thankful that he considered the
感谢他考虑过
scriptures that day I'm glad that he's
经文那天我很高兴他是
willing to talk honestly about what was
愿意诚实地谈论什么是
going on in his life it was a blessing
在他的生命中继续这是一种祝福
to communicate the gospel with a heart
用心去传播福音
of love for this young man and to this
对这个年轻人和对此的爱
day I pray for the day that he responds
一天，我祈求他回应 的日子
to that true gospel so how should we
那个真正的福音所以我们应该怎样
counsel the person who professes faith
劝告自称信仰的人
and repentance in response to the gospel
为了回应福音而悔改
but either lacks discernible fruit or
但要么缺乏可辨别的水果，要么
has serious or long-term sin in his
在他的身上有严重或长期的罪
present life this is the state of many
现在的生活这是许多人的状态
counsel ease when they come to us after
他们来之后来找我们的安慰
using the Scriptures to discern as much
使用圣经来辨别尽可能多
heart information as possible if there's
心脏信息如果可能的话
no clear information on on this person
没有关于此人的明确信息
the person who's responded to the gospel
那个回应福音的人
and faith and repentance that there is
与信仰和忏悔，有
no discernable fruit if we we assume
如果我们假设，没有可辨别的水果
that they are a Christian we take their
他们是基督徒，我们采取他们的
word for their response to the gospel
他们对福音的回应
with that counsel II as counseling
以律师二作为辅导
progresses one of three options will
进步的三个选项之一将
become apparent either the counsel E is
律师E是显而易见的
a sinning believer who's at the low
一个犯罪信徒谁是在低
point of his spiritual life or number
他的精神生活或数 点
two the counsel II is a professing
二，律师二是自称
believer who refused
拒绝的信徒
uses to repent from serious sins or
用来忏悔严重的罪恶或
number three the council he has been
他去过的理事会排名第三
around the church for a long time but
在教堂周围很长一段时间但是
has never responded to the gospel in
从来没有回应 了福音
each case as we get to know and
每个案例我们都知道并且
understand that person and their
了解那个人和他们
response to God's Word and to the gospel
回应上帝的话语和福音
itself
本身
we provide truth from the word necessary
我们从必要的词语中提供真相
to enable that council to respond to God
以使该委员会，以回应神
in faith repentance obedience or the
信仰悔改服从或悔改
necessary combination thereof our
必要的组合我们
mission is to make disciples Matthew 8
任务是使门徒马修8
or 28 19 and 20 so the accurate
或28 19和20所以准确
communication of the gospel is essential
传播福音是至关重要的
for the salvation of a soul and the
为了拯救灵魂和灵魂
corresponding beginning of a new life in
相应的新生活开始
Christ what I'd like to do in our next
基督在接下来的事情中我想做什么
few minutes is point out briefly some
几分钟简要地指出一些
important aspects of the gospel
福音的重要方面
regarding this unbelieving or perhaps
对于这种不信或或许
very image for Christian take a look at
非常形象为基督徒看看
page 107 top of the page and we'll look
第107 页，我们将看看
at point B for the unsaved council II
在B点为未得救的理事会II
the cross of Christ the cross of Christ
基督的十字架是基督的十字架
is the focal point of our salvation
是我们救赎的焦点
human sin required the just penalty of
人类的罪恶需要得到正义的惩罚
death and only the sinless son of God
死亡，只有上帝无罪的儿子
could pay the price for others it's so
可以为其他人付出代价
vital for us with people who are either
对于我们这些人来说至关重要
very image for Christians or who are not
基督徒或非基督徒的形象
believers at all to have the focal point
信徒们都有焦点
of our communication be the cross of
我们的沟通是十字架的
Jesus Christ
耶稣基督
these truths from the word God will use
这些真理来自上帝将使用的词
to to impact the soul point-c repentance
要影响灵魂点c忏悔
repentance is not a source of salvation
悔改不是拯救的源泉
apart from the gospel rather it is part
除了福音，它是一部分
of the response of faith by one
一个人的信仰反应
receiving the gospel and it's a
接受福音，这是一个
manifestation of faith in Jesus Christ
表达对耶稣基督的信仰
as Savior and Lord
作为救主和主
so repentance is essential in salvation
所以悔改在救恩中是必不可少的
Jesus taught that keeping his
耶稣教导他保持他的
Commandments results in abiding in his
诫命导致他的。
love according to John 15:10 if a person
根据 一个人如果到约15:10爱
could be saved by faith without
没有，可以凭信心得救
repenting that statement wouldn't be
忏悔那句话不会
correct so the lordship of Christ as
正确的，所以基督的主权是
taught in first John and Galatians 1:10
在约翰和加拉太书1:10中教导
in Galatians 2:20 implies that
在加拉太书2:20意味着
repentance is part of saving faith this
悔改是拯救信仰的一部分
is an important matter in our time point
在我们的时间点是一个重要的问题
D regeneration regeneration is the
D再生再生是
beginning of a new spiritual life that
开始新的精神生命的
will go on for eternity this occurs at
将继续这种情况发生在
the precise instant that a person is
一个人的确切时刻
saved by responding to the facts of the
通过回应 事实来保存
gospel with faith and repentance it is
信仰和悔改的福音是
literally being born again people who
从字面上重生 的人谁
are never regenerated also exist forever
从来没有再生也永远存在
but their life after life on Earth
但是他们在地球上的生活
consists of what God calls eternal death
由上帝称为永恒的死亡组成
in torment alone in the dark and
在黑暗中独自受折磨
separated from the Almighty Creator
与全能的造物主分开
often regeneration occurs in the
经常再生发生在
biblical counseling room what a great
圣经咨询室真是太棒了
joy it is to pray as somebody responds
喜欢祈祷，因为有人回应
to the gospel in faith and repentance to
在信心和悔改的福音
see this new life begin may we each be
看到这个新的生命开始，我们每个人都可以
bold and clear in our proclamation of
在我们的宣言中大胆而明确
the gospel in the counseling room and in
咨询室和福音中的福音
all the other relationships with
所有其他关系
unbelievers that God has for us
上帝对我们 不信 的人
so scriptures declare that a man must be
所以经文宣称一个人必须是
regenerated by God before he can see God
在他能看见上帝之前，由上帝重生
that's what Jesus said to Nicodemus in
这就是耶稣对尼哥底母说的话
John 3:3 through 21 point II
约翰福音3：3 到21点二
justification the Bible teaches that
圣经教导的理由
every person who is forgiven for sin
每个被宽恕罪恶的人
through the sacrifice of Jesus Christ is
通过耶稣基督的牺牲是
justified at the point in time where
在时间点在哪里有道理
regeneration occurs this basic truth of
再生发生了这个基本的事实
the gospel is really helpful for your
福音真的对你有帮助
young believers who are Christians to
作为基督徒的年轻信徒
understand where they are with Christ in
了解他们与基督的关系
thinking about it
思考它
justification is a legal term which is
理由是一个合法的术语
equivalent to declaring a person not
相当于宣布一个人不是
guilty in a courtroom so the picture of
在法庭上有罪如此照片
justification in the scriptures is this
经文中的理由是这样的
it's a courtroom and God is the just
这是一个法庭，上帝是公正的
judge and the sinful man is guilty Jesus
法官和有罪的人是有罪的耶稣
Christ the agent of propitiation the one
基督是赎罪的代理人之一
who paid the price for our guilt is just
为我们的内疚付出代价的只是
and God who justifies us through the
神谁证明我们通过
work of Jesus Christ is just also he's
耶稣基督的 工作也只是他的
fair were guilty of the sin there's a
公平犯罪是有罪的
penalty for the sin but the penalty has
惩罚罪，但惩罚有
been paid so the result is the redeemed
已经支付，结果是赎回
sinner is justified is declared not
罪人被证明是合理的
guilty by the just and righteous judge a
公正和正义的法官犯了罪
justification is explained in Romans
罗马人解释了理由
five one and two that's in your notes
你的笔记中有五个一个和两个
therefore having been justified by faith
因此被信仰证明是正当的
we have peace with God through our Lord
我们通过我们的主与上帝和好
Jesus Christ through whom also we have
我们也有耶稣基督
obtained our introduction by faith into
得到了我们的信仰介绍
this grace in which we stand
这恩典中我们的立场
we exalt in the hope of the glory of God
我们高举希望荣耀上帝
friends may we be strong and clear in
朋友们，我们可能会变得强大和清晰
our explanation of the gospel from an
我们对福音的解释
accurate theology as we communicate to
我们沟通的准确神学
the unsaved people God brings into our
上帝带给我们的未得救的人
lives may he be honored by our high
生活可能会受到我们的高度的尊重
regard for his plan of salvation as it's
他的 拯救 计划，因为它是关于
revealed in the scriptures may he be
在经文中透露可能是他
honored by our genuine love and care for
我们真诚的爱和关怀使我们感到荣幸
each lost soul that he brings across our
他带给我们的 每一个失去的灵魂
path and maybe he may he be glorified
路径，也许他可能会得到荣耀
and honored by our intense desire that
我们强烈的愿望使我感到荣幸
each one of those comes to Christ in
每个人都来到基督里面
faith and repentance so the way for the
信仰和忏悔所以的方式
unsaved counsel ly to deal with sin is
未得救的律师应对罪恶
to be forgiven by responding to the
通过回应来得到宽恕
gospel in faith and repentance next
接下来信仰福音和悔改
we'll consider common issues for the
我们会考虑的常见问题
Christian and how he or she deals with
克里斯蒂安以及他或她如何处理
sin Roman numeral three is guilt that's
罪孽罗马数字三是有罪的
at the top of page 108 point ay Christ
在第108页的顶部指出基督
has taken away the guilt of Christians
已经剥夺了基督徒的罪恶感
in regard to judgment second Corinthians
关于第二次哥林多前书的审判
5:21 describes the great exchange that
5:21 描述了巨大的对攻
God has caused between every Christian
上帝造就了每一个基督徒
and Jesus Christ second Corinthians 5:21
和耶稣基督第二次哥林多前书5:21
quote he made him who knew no sin to be
引用他让他知道没有罪的人
sin on our behalf that we might become
代表我们犯罪，我们可能成为
the righteousness of God in him
上帝的正义在他里面
he took our sin on himself and suffered
他把自己的罪孽带走了自己并受了苦
the wrath of God and he suffered the
上帝的愤怒和他遭受了
shame of our sin as well and then here
我们的罪也羞辱 然后在这里
we are justified through Jesus Christ
我们通过耶稣基督得到称义
and we have been given his righteousness
我们得到了他的正义
so we have no guilt in God's court
所以我们在上帝的法庭上没有罪恶感
because Jesus Christ paid the debt for
因为耶稣基督偿还了债务
our sin that's the great truth for us
我们的罪，这是我们的伟大真理
and for every Christian counsel II who
和每一个基督徒律师II谁
comes across our path this is huge
遇到了我们的道路，这是巨大的
because sometimes the person who's
因为有时候是那个人
coming to you for counseling has had the
来找你咨询已经有了
same sin for 26 years or they've
同样的罪恶26年或他们已经
committed some serious sin that they
他们犯了一些严重的罪
never thought they could possibly do but
从没想过他们可能会这样做
they did true Christians are never in
他们做了真正的基督徒从来没有
danger of losing their salvation we know
我们知道，失去救恩的危险
that because of what Jesus said in John
因为耶稣在约翰所说的话
10 god is greatest' there's no one
10 上帝是最伟大的'没有人
greater than him and he will not allow
大于他，他不会允许
anyone to snatch a believer out of his
任何人都可以从他的手中抢夺一个信徒
hand
手
1st Peter 1:3 through 5 says that he
彼得前书1：3到5说他
protects us with his power the Almighty
用全能的力量保护我们
God who created the universe and will
创造宇宙和意志的 上帝
destroy with an intense heat one day he
他有一天会被强烈的热量摧毁
protects you and I with his power for
用他的力量保护你和我
that salvation ready to be revealed in
那个救恩准备好了
the last time our salvation is secure
我们的救赎最后一次是安全的
the Bible teaches that there are two
圣经教导说有两个
aspects of our relationship with God one
我们与上帝关系的一个方面
is the judicial we've been talking about
是我们一直在谈论的司法
that in God's court every Christian is
每个基督徒都在上帝的宫廷里
not guilty due to propitiation for the
由于赎罪 而无罪
through the death of Jesus Christ
通过耶稣基督的死亡
there's also a second aspect of our
这里还有第二方面 我们
relationship with God
与上帝的关系
that's the parental relationship that he
那是他的父母关系
has with each of us this encompasses our
我们每个人都有这个包含我们的
day-to-day interactions with him in the
与他的日常互动
judicial relationship we have with God
我们与上帝的司法关系
we have no guilt now nor will we ever
我们现在也没有内疚，也不会
have any guilt before him because Jesus
因为耶稣，在他面前有任何罪恶感
Christ has taken that conversely in
基督反过来采取了相反的行动
regard to discipline this is point B
关于纪律， 这是B点
Christians do have guilt for sin as
基督徒确实对罪有罪
Christians we are forgiven judicially
基督徒我们在司法上得到宽恕
but as long as we're still alive on
但只要我们还活着上
earth we do sin first on 1:8 says that
地球我们先在1：8上犯罪
if we say we have no sin we're deceiving
如果我们说我们没有罪，我们就是在欺骗
ourselves and the truth is not in us we
自己和真理不在我们，我们
will not be perfect while we're living
我们生活的时候不会是完美的
here in the parental relationship we
在这里我们的父母关系
have with God we do have guilt for these
与上帝同在， 我们对这些感到内疚
sins in fact severe or long-term sin
事实上，罪是严重的或长期的罪
invites God's discipline according to
按照上帝的纪律来接受上帝的训练
1st Corinthians 5 9 to 13 and Hebrews 12
哥林多前书5章9至13章和希伯来书12章
5 through 11 because he is a loving
5到11 因为他是一个爱人
father if we persist in sin or commit
父亲，如果我们坚持犯罪或犯罪
serious sin God will bring pain and
严重的罪恶上帝会带来痛苦和痛苦
hardship into our lives
困难进入我们的生活
he'll discipline us to bring us to our
他会训练我们把我们带到我们的身边
senses at which point we as Christians
感觉到我们作为基督徒
will come to our senses and will repent
我们会感觉到并会悔改
from that sin and be restored to him
从那罪中恢复到他身上
we'll rely on his sufficient word to
我们将依靠他足够的话语
replace that sin with righteousness
用正义代替罪
many council leaves are in the midst of
许多议会的叶子都在中间
this interaction with God they've had
他们 与上帝的这种互动
long-term or serious sin and some are
长期或严重的罪恶，有些是
experiencing in one way or another the
经历这样或那样的
discipline of God so this is our topic
上帝的纪律所以这是我们的主题
for the hour dealing with sin biblically
在圣经中处理罪恶的时间
our purpose in counseling is to instruct
我们在咨询方面的目的是指导
that counsel II to deal with sin
律师二来处理罪
biblically and the result of that will
圣经和那个结果会
be restoration to God in the parental
在父母身上恢复上帝
relationship in a few minutes we'll
我们会在几分钟内建立关系
discuss the specific steps the Bible
讨论圣经的具体步骤
gives us for alleviating God's
让我们减轻上帝的压力
discipline and our guilt in that
纪律和我们的内疚
parental relationship with God first
父母先与上帝保持关系
though I'd like us to look at Point C
虽然我希望我们看看C点
which is unbiblical solutions to guilt
这是对罪恶的不符合圣经的解决方案
in our culture many people teach or
在我们的文化中， 许多人教或
practice solutions to guilt that are
实践有罪的解决方案
apart from the Bible's plan for dealing
除了圣经的交易计划
with guilt these solutions are sometimes
有时候这些解决方案有罪
applied to the guilt of the unbeliever
适用于不信者的内疚
sins and other times the guilt
罪恶和其他时间的内疚
Christians have before God as their
基督徒在上帝面前是他们的
father here are some of those errant
这里的父亲是一些错误的人
solutions to guilt one is unbiblical
有罪的解决方案是不符合圣经的
anthropology every child is pure see how
人类学每个孩子都是纯粹的看待如何
that works that is an attempt to solve
这是尝试解决的问题
man's problem of guilt for sin because
男人对罪的内疚问题因为
it's teaching us that yeah I was born
它告诉我们，是的，我出生了
pure I'm good and so why is it their sin
纯洁， 我很好，所以为什么是他们的罪
in my life oh it's because of the the
在我的生活哦，这是因为 在
things that other people did to me and
别人对我做的事情
I'm I can't help it I'm just reacting to
我是无法帮助的，我只是在做出反应
it but it's not my fault because at the
但它不是我的错，因为在
core and when I was born I was pure
核心， 当我出生时，我是纯洁的
another unbiblical solution to guilt is
对内疚的另一个不符合圣经的解决方案是
misleading terminology he suffers from
他误导的误导性术语
the disease of alcoholism the Bible
圣经中酗酒的疾病
calls drunkenness a sin
把醉酒称为罪
but if it's a disease then there's no
但如果它是一种疾病， 那就没有了
guilt for them if somehow if somehow I
如果以某种方式内疚他们，如果不知何故，我
have cancer well it's not it's I'm not
患癌症不是我不是
guilty for that it's a disease that
因为这是一种疾病而感到内疚
somehow occurred in my body so the
某种程度上发生在我的身体所以
terminology of disease is really
疾病的术语确实如此
misleading and not accurate biblically
误导而且不符合圣经
there's also not taking responsibility
也没有承担责任
for sin when we say things like she made
当我们说出她做的事情时，为了罪
me so mad
我很生气
CA I'm sinning by being angry but when I
加州我生气了，但是当我生气的时候
think that I'm saying she made me mad
我想我说她让我发疯了
there's also blame-shifting
也有责备转移
he sins because he's a victim of the
他犯了罪，因为他是这个人的受害者
sins against him during a difficult
在艰难的过程中犯了罪
childhood and there are also chemical
童年时代也有化学物质
solutions to sin many people would say
许多人会说，罪的解决方案
when I am angry a few drinks calm my
当我生气的时候喝几杯让我平静下来
nerves and get me in a better mood Freud
紧张， 让我心情更好弗洛伊德
claimed that the misdeeds of adults were
声称成年人的罪行是
due to wrong suffered during childhood
由于童年时期遭受的错误
in his mind those included preachers and
在他的脑海里那些包括传教士和
parents who taught that sin was wrong
教导罪是错的父母
unless you think that this these
除非你认为这些
unbiblical kinds of justification of sin
不符合圣经的罪的称义
is outdated think about this one of the
已经过时了想到这一个
most downloaded songs in 2011 is a song
2011年大多数下载的歌曲都是一首歌
sung by pink and she says this in the
粉红色唱，她说这个
chorus pretty pretty please if you ever
合唱相当漂亮，如果你曾经
ever feel you're less than perfect
永远觉得你不够完美
you're perfect to me that's an
你是完美的我是一个
unbiblical anthropology and it's a
不符合圣经的人类学，它是一个
popular message well each of these
流行信息以及每个这些
unbiblical solutions to guilt needs to
对罪恶需要的不符合 圣经的解决方案
be replaced in the counseling room by
在咨询室被替换
the the true way to alleviate guilt the
减轻罪恶感的真正方法
biblical
圣经
way of dealing with sin one other
处理罪恶的方式
section in this category what does the
这个类别中的部分是什么
Bible say about guilt we are responsible
圣经说我们有责任感到内疚
for the sins we commit James 1:14 and 15
因为我们犯了雅各书1:14和15的罪
says that we are responsible but each
说我们负责但每个人都有责任
one is tempted when he is carried away
当他被带走 时，一个人会受到诱惑
and enticed by his own lust then when
然后被他自己的欲望所诱惑
lust has conceived it gives birth to sin
欲望构想它会生出罪恶
we're also responsible for the good
我们也对好事负责
things that we do not do James 4:17
我们不做的事雅各书4:17
therefore to the one who knows the right
因此对知道权利的人
thing to do and does not do it to him it
要做的事情，不要对他这样做
is sin so judicially before God we have
在我们拥有的上帝之前，这是一种司法上的罪
no guilt and our salvation in Christ is
在基督里没有内疚和我们的救恩
absolutely secure in God's parental
在上帝的父母身上绝对安全
relationship we do have guilt so in
联系我们确实有内疚所以在
section 4 of our study we'll examine
我们将研究我们研究的第4部分
what the Bible teaches that Christians
圣经教给基督徒的是什么
must do to deal with sin biblically the
必须做的是以圣经的方式 处理罪恶
first thing is confess first John 1:9 if
首先是承认约翰福音1：9如果
we confess our sins he is faithful and
我们承认我们的罪，他是信实的，
righteous to forgive us our sins and to
义赦免我们的 罪，
cleanse us from all unrighteousness the
清除我们所有不义之物
word confess is the greek homologa it
单词confess 是希腊语homologa它
means literally to say the same thing
字面意思是说同样的事情
the tense of the verb shows that it's an
动词的时态表明它是一个
ongoing action so if we agree with God
如果我们同意上帝的话，正在采取行动
about our sins then what will we think
关于我们的罪，那么我们会怎么想
well one will hate our sin God hates sin
一个人会恨我们的罪， 上帝恨恶罪恶
and that's apparent in passages like
这在像这样的段落中很明显
proverbs 6 16 to 22 that passage lists 6
谚语6 16至22，段落6
things that the Lord hates all but one
主讨厌别人的事
of those is a sin and the other one is
那些是一种罪过，另一种是
the mo
莫
motive behind sins that's a heart that
罪恶背后的动机是一颗心
devises wicked plans so if I would agree
制定邪恶的计划，如果我同意的话
with God about my sin then I hate it
与上帝有关我的罪，然后我讨厌它
also psalm 32 3 through 5 describes the
还有诗篇323到5描述了
second aspect of confessing sin to God
向上帝承认罪的第二个方面
using that term confessed to denote
使用该术语承认表示
admitting guilt
承认内疚
it says when I kept silent about my sin
它说当我对我的罪保持沉默
my body wasted away through my groaning
我的身体因呻吟而浪费掉了
all day long for day and night your hand
白天和黑夜的一整天你的手
was heavy upon me my vitality was
我的生命力很重要
drained away as with the fever heat of
随着发烧的热量消失了
summer I acknowledged my sin to you and
夏天， 我承认我的罪你和
my iniquity I did not hide I said I will
我的罪孽我没有隐藏我说我会
confess my transgressions to the Lord
向主承认我的过犯
and you forgave the guilt of my sin so
而你原谅了我的罪恶
the first thing to do in dealing with
的第一件事就是在处理做
sin is to confess it to God that
罪就是向上帝承认
includes coming to the conclusion that I
包括得出结论我
hate my sin and admitting to God that I
恨我的罪，向我承认我
did sin the second thing that we must do
做了我们必须做的第二件事
to deal with our own symbol eclis is to
处理我们自己的符号eclis是
repent revelation 3:19 Jesus in a real
悔改启示3:19 耶稣在真实中
letter to real Christians warned them
致真正基督徒的信告诉他们
about the need to repent of their sins
关于需要悔改他们的罪过
he said therefore those whom I love I
因此他说那些我爱我的人
reprove and discipline therefore be
责备，因此纪律是
zealous and repent so what are the steps
热心和忏悔所以步骤是什么
to repentance first turn away from sin
悔改首先转离罪恶
proverbs 28:13 says it this way he who
箴言28:13这样说他是谁
conceals his transgressions will not
隐瞒他的过犯不会
prosper but he who confesses and
繁荣， 但他承认和
forsakes them will find compassion
放弃他们会找到同情心
second real repentance includes a
第二次真正的忏悔包括一个
genuine regret over sin in first
首先是对罪的真正后悔
Corinthians seven nine and ten Paul
哥林多人七九十保罗
commends Christians who have repented
赞扬已经悔改的基督徒
from sin in this way
以这种方式来自罪
he says I now rejoice not that you were
他说我现在不喜欢你
made sorrowful but that you were made
悲伤， 但你成了
sorrowful to the point of repentance for
悲伤到悔改的地步
you were made sorrowful according to the
根据你的说法，你变得悲伤
will of God for sorrow that is according
上帝的意志是悲伤的
to the will of God produces a repentance
上帝的旨意产生悔改
without regret leading to salvation but
没有后悔导致拯救但是
the salvation of the world produces
世界的救赎产生了
death repentance with regret is the
遗憾的死亡忏悔是
sorrow of the world that might be
可能是世界的悲伤
expressed something like this I won't do
表达了这样的事我不会这样做
it again because I don't want my wife to
它再次因为我不想要我的妻子
leave me but I sure did have fun that
离开我，但我确实很开心
weekend see that's repentance with
周末看到忏悔了
regret or the eleven year olds version I
后悔或十一岁的版本我
deserved the punishment but it was worth
应得的惩罚，但它是值得的
it to post those private photos each of
它发布每个私人照片
those two repented but they regret they
那两个人后悔了，但他们后悔了
won't be able to enjoy the passing
将不能享受传球
pleasures of that sin again but this
这个罪的乐趣再次出现了
repentance the biblical repentance
悔改圣经的悔改
without regret might be spoken in words
没有后悔可能会用语言说出来
like these in prayer I genuinely regret
像祷告中的这些我真的很后悔
my sins not because of their
我的罪不是因为他们的罪
consequences but because I sinned
后果， 但因为我犯了罪
against you lord
反对你的主人
that's the repentance that pleases God
那是上帝喜悦的悔改
third aspect of repentance repentance
悔改悔改的第三个方面
includes turning to righteousness Romans
包括转向正义的罗马人
6 11 and 12 and 19 tells us how to think
6 11和12和19告诉我们如何思考
and act as believers it says even so
并作为它的信徒说，即使如此
consider yourselves to be dead to sin
认为自己是 死的罪
but alive to God in Christ Jesus
但在基督耶稣里活在上帝面前
therefore do not let sin
所以不要犯罪
in your mortal body that you should obey
在你的凡人身上，你应该服从
its lusts so now present your members as
它的欲望如此呈现给你的成员
slaves of righteousness resulting in
正义的奴隶导致了
sanctification
圣化
so repentance is turning away from sin
因此悔改是从罪转身离开
and turning to righteousness
并转向正义
Wayne Mack describes biblical counseling
韦恩麦克描述了圣经辅导
cases where sin is the primary issue in
罪是主要问题的案例
this way he says everything before
这样他就说出了一切
repentance is pointing to it and
悔改指向它和
everything after repentance is pointing
忏悔之后的一切都在指向
back to it I think that's true when sin
回到它我认为这是真的，当罪恶
is the main issue in a biblical
是圣经中的主要问题
counseling case everything we're doing
咨询案例我们正在做的一切
with that believer before repentance is
在悔改之前与那位信徒相处
pointing them to the need to turn away
指出他们需要转身离开
from their sin and to God by God's grace
从上帝的恩典到他们的罪和上帝
and through the sufficient word to make
并通过足够的话来说明
that decision
那个决定
I intend to not sin in that way again
我打算不再那样犯罪了
and then everything after that is
再其后 的 内容
helping them make that decision a
帮助他们作出这样的决定一
pattern of living through the word
通过这个词生活的模式
through the specific discipleship and
通过具体的门徒训练和
the general discipleship they become
他们成为一般的门徒训练
mature believers who have a habit
有习惯的成熟信徒
pattern of honoring God in that in other
在其他方面尊重上帝的模式
areas of life so repentance is vital
生活领域如此忏悔至关重要
there's a third requirement for the
还有第三个要求
Christian to deal with sin biblically
基督徒用圣经来对付罪
and that is make restitution we make
这就是我们做出的恢复原状
restitution for loss incurred by those
归还那些人所遭受的损失
we sinned against Matthew 5 23 and 24
我们犯了马太福音5章23和24
therefore if you are presenting your
因此，如果你正在展示你的
offering at the altar and there remember
在祭坛上献祭并记得
that your brother has something against
你兄弟反对的东西
you leave your offering there before the
你把它放在那里之前
altar and go first be reconciled to your
祭坛，先和你的和解
brother and then present your offering
兄弟，然后提出你的产品
restitution regard requires the effort
恢复原状需要努力
the money and/or
钱和/或
time to return the property of the
是时候归还了
person sinned against to its previous
这个人犯了以前的罪
state the fourth requirement for dealing
说明交易的第四个要求
with sin biblically is obey the law
以圣经的方式遵守罪是遵守律法的
romans 13 1 through 4 establishes the
罗马书13 1到4确立了
laws of this nation as being established
这个国家的法律正在建立之中
by God for the blessing of the one who
由上帝赐予那个人的祝福
does right and as an Avenger who brings
做得对，作为带来的复仇者
wrath upon the one who practices evil
对犯罪的人施以愤怒
some sins bring legal consequences if
如果，有些罪会带来法律后果
the law requires disclosure of sin by
法律要求披露罪
the counsel II or the counselor we obey
律师 II或我们听从 辅导员
the law and we direct the counsel ease
法律和我们指导律师轻松
to obey the law
遵守法律
in such cases the law including the
在这种情况下，法律， 包括
prison system is an instrument of God's
监狱系统是上帝的工具
discipline and his justice so confess
纪律和他的正义如此承认
repent make restitution obey the law
悔改使恢复原状服从法律
those are the biblical steps for a
这些是圣经的步骤
Christian dealing with sin in my own
基督徒在我自己的处理罪
home practicing these things was
家里练习这些东西是
something they changed our lives for
他们改变了我们的生活
Julie and I and Sky and ELISA living by
Julie和我和Sky和ELISA一起生活
these truth of the word was extremely
这个词的真相非常
helpful early in our days as a family we
我们作为一个家庭在我们的早期很有帮助
would deal with sin not in the biblical
会不会在圣经中处理罪
way usually if there was some big
通常如果有一些大的方式
conflict or somebody had sinned against
冲突或有人犯了罪
the other there would be a period of
另一个会有一段时间
silence just not much talking or
沉默只是说话或说话
interaction going on for a couple of
互动持续了几个
days and then we would I guess
天，然后我们会猜
eventually decided that we needed to
最终决定我们需要
move on with life and so we'd resumed
继续生活，所以我们恢复了
where we were before but after
我们之前但之后的地方
considering these truths of the word we
考虑到我们这个词的这些真理
had we made it a practice of the for
曾经我们把它的一个做法
Christian buddies to deal with sin
基督徒哥们对付罪恶
biblically and so the emphasis was first
圣经，因此首先强调
on confessing sin and repenting in our
在承认我们的罪恶和忏悔
communication with God
与上帝沟通
than asking for forgiveness from each
而不是要求每个人的宽恕
other and then choosing to forgive and
其他然后选择原谅和
then there was that restoration with God
然后有与上帝的复原
and with each other
和彼此
the results were by God's grace our
结果是上帝的恩典我们的
identity as a family became for
作为一个家庭的身份成为
Christians within our roles within the
基督徒在我们的角色里面
family but for Christians who were
家人， 但对于那些曾经的基督徒
striving to become more like Christ and
努力变得更像基督和
by dealing with sin biblically it just
通过圣经的方式处理罪恶
opened the doors to to having this
有这个打开了大门
identity where each of us was a part of
我们每个人都参与其中的身份
the progress in sanctification in each
每个人的成圣进步
of the other three lives because we
其他三个生命因为我们
talked about these things openly and
公开谈论这些事情
honestly we confessed our sin and we
说实话，我们承认了我们的罪和我们
would even tell each other what the
甚至会告诉对方是什么
motive behind the sin was and then when
罪的背后是动机，然后是什么时候
we would forgive we would completely
我们会原谅我们会完全
forgive and so it was the end of the
原谅所以这是结束了
conflict everything was good between us
冲突一切都很好我们之间
after that God was very gracious and
在此之后，上帝非常仁慈
thankful for these truths of his word
感谢他的这些真理
and how he transformed one Christian
以及他如何改变一个基督徒
family through them well what is the
通过家庭以及他们是什么
counsel of the Bible for a Christian who
圣经的律师为一个基督徒
has been sinned against this is also
这也是犯了罪
something that is common to life for
生活中常见的东西
each of us and also is a common issue in
我们每个人也是一个共同的问题
the biblical counseling room
圣经咨询室
first Corinthians 13:5 talks about
哥林多前书13：5谈到
forgiveness it says love does not take
原谅它说爱不会
into account a wrong suffered Matthew
考虑到马修遭遇的错误
546 applies this to people outside of
546适用于以外的人
the Christian world it says we love not
基督教世界， 它说我们不爱
only our friends but also our enemies so
只有我们的朋友，而且 我们的敌人如此
Christians forgive unconditionally this
基督徒无条件地原谅这一点
does not mean that the person who sinned
并不意味着犯罪的人
against us is not subject to the
反对我们不受制于
righteous consequences of their sin such
他们的罪的正义后果如此
as parental discipline or enforcement of
作为父母的纪律或执行
the law or church discipline or divorce
法律或教会纪律或离婚
or the need to make restitution but it
或者需要恢复原状
does mean this the Christian sinned
这意味着基督徒犯了罪
against chooses
反对选择
this I forgive therefore I no longer
这个我原谅我不再
think about or speak about those sins or
想想还是谈论这些罪或
hurt or stand opposed to that person I
伤害或反对那个人我
only speak about the sins for the
只谈论罪的罪
purposes of loving and helping that
爱和帮助是目的
person to either come to salvation or to
人要么来拯救或
grow in sanctification Ephesians 4:32
以弗所书4:32成圣
teaches that same principle be kind to
教导同样的原则是善良的
one another tender-hearted forgiving
彼此温柔的原谅
each other just as God in Christ is also
正如在基督里的上帝一样，彼此也是如此
forgiving you I'm aware that there are
原谅你，我知道有
some different views on this but my view
我对此有一些不同的看法
is that because that's in Ephesians 4
是因为那是在以弗所书4章
not in Ephesians one through three where
不是在以弗所书中的一到三所在的地方
he says forgive as God in Christ has
他说，作为原谅神在基督里有
forgiven you I don't think he's talking
原谅你我不认为他在说话
about the forgiveness of when we came to
关于我们何时来到的宽恕
Christ that was the theology of
基督是神学的
Ephesians one through three this is in
以弗所书一到三，这就是
the application section of four through
通过四个应用部
six so where he says forgive each other
六岁的他说，原谅对方
just as God in Christ has forgiven you I
正如神在基督里已经原谅你了我
think he's talking to us as Christians
以为他是在跟我们说基督徒
and how has God in Christ forgiven us in
以及上帝在基督里如何原谅我们
the new covenant he chooses to remember
他选择记住的新约
our sins no more practically how can a
我们的罪孽几乎没有了
Christian forgive jesus answered that
克里斯蒂安原谅耶稣回答说
question in matthew 18 21 to 35 jesus
问题在马修1821至35耶稣
christ was asked about forgiving when
基督被问到宽恕何时
it's difficult the disciples asked him
门徒们很难问他
Lord how often shall my brother sin
主啊， 我哥哥经常犯罪
against me and I forgive him up to seven
反对我，我原谅他七个
times sounded pretty impossible and then
时间听起来很不可能然后
Jesus said here's a way to forgive an
耶稣说这是一种原谅的方式
unlimited amount of times when they sin
他们犯罪时无限次
against you and so he tells the familiar
反对你，所以他告诉熟悉的
story of the man who amassed so large a
积累了如此大的男人的故事
debt that he couldn't possibly repay it
债务，他不可能偿还
it would be like for most of us if you
对我们大多数人来说，如果你
or I owed 40 million dollars to somebody
或者我欠了4000万美元给某人
and you added it all up in your mind and
你把它全部添加到了你的脑海里
you thought if I work a hundred hours a
你想，如果我的工作一百个小时
week and I live to be 84 I won't be
一周，我活到84岁，我不会
close that's the idea but then somehow
关闭这个想法但不知何故
he's forgiven that amount the amount he
他原谅了这个金额
could never repay and then a short time
永远不会偿还，然后很短的时间
later he's choking the guy who owes in
后来他窒息了那个欠他的人
three months wages that's interesting
三个月的工资很有意思
he's not choking him over ten bucks for
他不呛他十块钱
lunch he's you know it's a significant
午餐，他知道这很重要
amount of money three months of wages
金额3个月工资
probably what's that like for the
可能是什么样的
average Americans $15,000
美国人平均15,000美元
somewhere in there so it's a significant
在那里的某个地方， 这是一个重要的
amount of money but but compared to what
的金额，但比起但什么
he's been forgiven you know it's really
他被宽恕了，你知道这是真的
small the point of the story is the
小故事的重点是
forgiving man was a fool he had been
宽恕男人是个傻瓜
forgiven the insurmountable debt and
原谅了不可逾越的债务和
he's choking the other man over a
他窒息了另一个男人
significant debt but nevertheless a way
重大债务，但仍然是一种方式
smaller amount by the blood of Jesus
耶稣的血少量
Christ you and I have been forgiven
基督你和我都被宽恕了
the equivalent of a 40 million dollar
相当于4000万美元
debt a debt that we could never repay if
债务是我们永远无法偿还的债务
I think rightly about that I will gladly
我认为我很乐意
forgive anyone who sinned against me or
原谅任何对我犯罪的人
my family even if the sin is seriously
我的家人， 即使罪是认真的
the $15,000 level of sin so here's my
15,000美元的罪恶水平所以这是我的
practical advice for people who struggle
为奋斗的人提供实用的建议
to forgive this is what I tell people to
原谅这就是我告诉人们
do and this is what I do when I struggle
这就是我奋斗时所做的事
with forgiving first I use a graphic
先宽恕我用图形
passage like Psalm 22 14 to 19 or isaiah
诗篇22 14至19或以赛亚书
53:3 through five they're printed for
他们打印的是53：3到5
you their passages are described in
你在他们的段落描述
graphic detail the price for my sin
图形细节我的罪的价格
Jesus Christ's dying to pay the price
耶稣基督渴望付出代价
and then I think about I meditate on
然后我想到我默想
Jesus Christ there on the cross and I
耶稣基督在十字架和我
start thinking about the worst sins that
开始考虑最坏的罪
I ever committed in my life I usually
我经常在我的生活中 犯下过
don't get very far down that list but
不要在那个列表上走得很远但是
before I come to my senses but I started
在我醒悟之前，我开始了
thinking through the worst things I ever
思考我曾经做过的最糟糕的事情
did the worst sins against the Lord with
用最坏的罪行对抗了主
that picture of Jesus Christ on the
那张耶稣基督的照片
cross paying for them what conclusion
交叉支付给他们什么结论
can you come to at a time like that and
你能来这样的时间吗？
Lord thank you thank you for paying the
主啊，谢谢你，感谢你付出了代价
price for my sin Lord God thank you for
我的罪的价格 主上帝，谢谢你
causing me to believe in the gospel what
让我相信福音是什么
an incredible thing it is to be forgiven
这是令人难以置信的事情，是被宽恕的
for a lifetime of sin and then we come
为了一生的罪，然后我们来
back to reality and we realize that
回到现实，我们意识到这一点
somebody in the family said something
家里有人说了些什么
rude to me an hour ago and it's not very
一个小时前对我很粗鲁，这不是很好
very hard to forgive or somebody did
非常难以原谅或有人这样做
something serious to you or someone in
事情严重到你或在
your family and you realize in honor of
你的家人，你实现了荣誉
Jesus Christ in honor of the amazing
耶稣基督以纪念这个令人惊叹的
grace of God that has forgiven me all of
上帝的恩典已经原谅了我所有人
those sins and the lifetime of sins how
那些罪， 罪怎样的寿命
can I do anything else but gladly
我可以做任何其他事情，但很乐意
forgive in one case in our biblical
原谅我们圣经中的一个案例
counseling center a man had committed
咨询中心一名男子已经承诺
adultery he had repented and he had
通奸他悔改了，他有
stayed away from temptation his wife had
远离他妻子的诱惑
been counseled at her church to go by
在她的教堂被劝告过去
her feelings and God they said would
她的感情和他们所说的上帝会
lead her through her emotions I asked
我问她带领她的情绪
her what was that like in a counseling
她在咨询中的表现如何
session where it's like going by your
会话就像你去的那样
feelings and she said I cried the whole
感觉，她说我哭了整整一个
time those were her feelings and why was
时间那些是她的感受，为什么
that she was so heard because her
因为她，所以她听到了
husband had been unfaithful and her fear
丈夫不忠心和她的恐惧
was that it if it ever happened again
是它，如果它再次发生
she would not be able to bear it in our
她将无法 承受它在我们的
counseling sessions she had seen that
她见过的咨询会
her husband had repented of sin and he
她的丈夫悔改了罪和他
was growing in righteousness but she
正在成长， 但她
refused to forgive him
拒绝原谅他
I showed her the passages we've looked
我向她展示了我们看过的段落
at in this section and she realized that
在本节中，她意识到了这一点
the Scriptures required her to forgive
圣经要求她原谅
him and so after thinking much about
他和 思考很多关于经过这么
Jesus Christ on the cross paying the
耶稣基督在十字架上支付
price for her since she did choose to
因为她选择了她的价格
forgive him soon they moved back into
他很快就原谅了他们搬回去了
the same house they were restored they
同样的房子，他们恢复了他们
walked with God together I want to tell
和神一起走，我想告诉你
you this part of it though later she
你这部分虽然后来她
told me why she did not want to forgive
告诉我她为什么 不想原谅
her husband this is how she said it I
她丈夫这就是她说的我
knew I had the golden ticket she said he
知道我有她说过的金票
had sinned against me greatly for the
为了这个 ，我犯了很大的罪
rest of my life if I did anything wrong
如果我做错了什么 ，我的余生
it would be his fault and then she said
这是他的错，然后她说
but the scripture showed me that I had
但经文告诉我，我有
to forgive sitting at the cross of
原谅坐在十字架上
Christ I made that decision I forgave
基督我做出了我原谅的决定
how could I do anything else point be
我怎么可能做别的点
dealing biblically with this the shame
以圣经的方式处理这种耻辱
of sin against you some sins carry with
罪恶对你的一些罪过
them the complication of shame we had
他们是我们羞耻的复杂因素
one counsel II who as a young girl was
一位律师二，作为一个年轻女孩
raped on many occasions and so later in
在很多场合被强奸等等
life that was a difficult thing not
生活是一件困难的事情
because only because she had been sinned
因为只是因为她犯了罪
against in such a detestable way but
以这种可恶的方式反对但是
also because her purity was taken away
也因为她的纯洁被带走了
she became a Christian but she still
她成了基督徒，但她仍然
struggled with that at 15 she knew that
在15岁的时候，她就知道这一点
she would not be a virgin on her wedding
她不会 在她的婚礼处女
night and so she was tempted to think
晚上，所以她很想想
about the shame she perceived herself to
关于她认为自己的耻辱
be unclean and impure but it wasn't
是不洁净和不纯洁的， 但事实并非如此
because she sinned it was because she
因为她犯了罪，这是因为她
was sinned against is there a biblical
被犯了罪，是否有圣经
solution for that kind of shame
这种耻辱的解决方案
absolutely first
绝对第一
she is justified as a gift by His grace
她被恩典称为礼物
through the redemption which is in
通过这是在 兑换
Christ Jesus
基督耶稣
Romans 3:24 in God's eyes she is
罗马书3:24在神的眼中，她是
completely clean despite having been
尽管已经完全干净了
sinned against we need her to dwell on
犯了罪，我们需要她去纠缠
that truth secondly Jesus Christ
那个真理其次是耶稣基督
suffered punishment not only for her sin
不仅因为她的罪受到了惩罚
but he also suffered humiliating public
但他也遭受了羞辱的公众
shame on the cross when you study that
你学习的时候十字架上的耻辱
in more detail you realize that in that
更详细地说，你意识到了这一点
culture unlike ours citizens did not
与我们的公民不同的文化没有
excuse the sins of people condemned
原谅被判谴责的人的罪行
under the law but public crucifixion it
根据法律但公开被钉十字架
wasn't a sad thing to the people but it
对人们来说并不是一件令人悲伤的事情
was an occasion to rejoice in justice
是一个为 正义 而高兴的机会
and to mock the criminals who deserved
并嘲笑应得的罪犯
to die
死
so Jesus Christ bore the shame of sin
所以耶稣基督承受了罪的耻辱
including the shame of being sinned
包括被犯罪耻
against it's such a joy to go through
反对它是一种如此快乐的经历
these truths of the word and for gals
这些词和gals的真相
like that to help her realize she is
像帮助她实现她
complete and pure in Christ she is loved
在基督里完全和纯洁，她被爱
by other believers the church regards
其他信徒对教会的看法
her as any other Christian woman and
她为任何其他基督教的女人，
that she has no shame because Jesus
因为耶稣 ，她没有羞耻
Christ bore her shame
基督使她感到羞耻
it's blessing in our Center to have a
在我们的中心有一个祝福
number of tremendous female counselors
一些巨大的女顾问
who counsel gals and situations like
谁劝告gals和情况
that in a way that's honoring to God and
在某种程度上这是荣耀上帝，
a blessing to them
祝福他们
in conclusion many counseling cases have
总之，许多咨询案例都有
at their core the problems of guilt are
在他们的核心是有罪的问题
the lack of restoration after sin
罪恶之后缺乏恢复
salvation through the gospel is God's
通过福音得救是上帝的
solution for the unbelievers guilt by
对不信之人有罪的解决办法
following the Bible's guidelines for
遵循圣经的指导方针
dealing with sin we as Christians will
处理罪我们作为基督徒会
be removed from the danger of God's
摆脱上帝的危险
discipline for severe or long-term sin
对严重或长期罪行的纪律
we will be we will forgive because we've
我们将会原谅，因为我们已经
been forgiven so much and we will find
得到了如此多的宽恕，我们会发现
full restoration with God in the
与上帝完全恢复
parental relationship and full
父母关系和充分
restoration with each other in your
在你的相处恢复
notes pages 1:12 - 1:15 are a synopsis
笔记页1:12  -  1:15是一个概要
of a study called a Christians guide to
一项名为“基督徒指南”的研究
dealing with sin that a couple of the
对付罪，一对夫妇的
pastors at Valley Bible Church and
谷圣经教堂的牧师和
myself have put together we have tried
我自己已经把我们试过了
to make that in a form to make it most
以一种形式使其成为最重要的
useful and beneficial for people like us
对我们这样的人有用和有益
as biblical counselors you're welcome to
作为圣经辅导员，欢迎你
use it and that's our gift to you from
使用它，这是我们给你 的礼物
the valley Bible Counseling Center
山谷圣经咨询中心
you
您